const all_questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "1. A Member of Parliament from Montreal announces that she will spend her weekend in her electoral district. This means she would be:",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "In the part of Montreal where she was elected. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "2. After a federal election, which party forms the new government?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "The party with the most elected representatives is invited by the Governor General to become the party in power. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 3, question: "3. Approximately how many Canadians served in the First World War?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "More than 600,000. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 4, question: "4. Canada has three territories and how many provinces?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "10 (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "5. Fatima is a new immigrant in Canada. What law allows her to take a job at par with a man?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Equality of women and men (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "6. From where does the name “Canada” come from?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: 'From "Kanata", the Huron-Iroquois word for village. (correct answer)',
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "7. Give an example of how you can show responsibility by participating in your community.",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Volunteer. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "8. Give an example of where English and French have equal status in Canada.",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "In the Parliament of Canada. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 9, question: "9. Give the first line of Canada’s national anthem?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "O Canada! Our home and native land! (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 10, question: "10. How are Members of Parliament chosen?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Elected by Canadian citizens. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "11. How are Senators chosen?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Senators are appointed by the Governor General on the advice of the Prime Minister. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "12. How does a bill become a law?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Approval by a majority in the House of Commons and Senate and finally the Governor General. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 13, question: "13. How is a Cabinet Minister chosen?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "By the Prime Minister (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "14. How is the government formed after a federal election?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Ordinarily, the party with the most elected representatives becomes the party in power. The leader of this party becomes the Prime Minister. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "15. How is the Prime Minister chosen?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "The leader of the party with the most elected representatives becomes the Prime Minister. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "16. In Canada, are you allowed to question the police about their service or conduct?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Yes, if you feel the need to. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "17. In Canada’s justice system what does “presumption of innocence” mean?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Everyone is innocent until proven guilty (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "18. In the 1960s, Quebec experienced an era of rapid change. What is this called?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "The Quiet Revolution. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 19, question: "19. In what industry do most Canadians work?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Service. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 20, question: "20. In which region do more than half the people in Canada live?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Central Canada. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "21. Name all the federal political parties in the House of Commons and their leaders",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Conservative (O'Toole), NDP (Singh), Liberal (Trudeau), Bloc Quebecois (Blanchet), Green Party (Paul) (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "22. Name six responsibilities of citizenship.",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer:
      "Obeying the law, taking responsibility for oneself and one's family, helping others in the community, voting in elections, serving on a jury, protecting and enjoying our heritage and environment. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 23, question: "23. Name the five regions of Canada", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Atlantic, Central, Prairie, West Coast, and North (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "24. Name three additional rights protected by the Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Mobility rights, Multiculturalism, and Aboriginal Peoples' rights. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "25. Name two fundamental freedoms protected by the Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms.",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Freedom of conscience and religion, and Freedom of association. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "26. Name two key documents that contain our rights and freedoms.",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms and Magna Carta (the Great Charter of Freedoms). (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 27, question: "27. Name two responsibilities of the federal government.", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "National defence and foreign policy. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 28, question: "28. Name two responsibilities of the provincial and territorial government.", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Health and Education (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 29, question: "29. On what date did Nunavut become a territory?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "April 1st, 1999 (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 30, question: "30. One third of all Canadians live in which province?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Ontario. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 31, question: "31. The Canadian Coat of Arms and motto is “A Mari Usque Ad Mare.” This means:", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "From sea to sea. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 32,
    question: "32. What are some examples of taking responsibility for yourself and your family?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Getting a job, taking care of one's family and working hard in keeping with one's abilities. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    question: "33. What are the Prairie provinces and their capital cities?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Alberta (Edmonton), Saskatchewan (Regina) and Manitoba (Winnipeg). (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    question: "34. What are the provinces of Central Canada and their capital cities?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Ontario (Toronto) and Quebec (Quebec City). (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    question: "35. What are the provinces of the Atlantic region and their capital cities?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Newfoundland and Labrador (St. John's), Nova Scotia (Halifax), New Brunswick (Fredericton) and Prince Edward Island (Charlottetown). (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    question: "36. What are the territories of Northern Canada and their capital cities?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Yukon Territory (Whitehorse), Northwest Territories (Yellowknife), and Nunavut (Iqaluit). (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    question: "37. What are the three levels of government in Canada?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Federal, Provincial and Territorial, Municipal (local). (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 38, question: "38. What are the three main groups of Aboriginal peoples?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "First Nations, Métis and Inuit. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 39,
    question: "39. What are the three main types of industry in Canada?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Natural resources, manufacturing and services. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 40, question: "40. What are the three parts of Parliament?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "The Sovereign, the House of Commons and the Senate. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 41, question: "41. What are the two official languages of Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "English and French. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 42, question: "42. What country is Canada’s largest trading partner?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "United States of America. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 43, question: "43. What did the Canadian Pacific Railway symbolize?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Unity. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 44,
    question: "44. What did the Fathers of Confederation do?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "They worked together to establish a new country, the Dominion of Canada (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 45, question: "45. What do you call a law before it is passed?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "A Bill. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 46, question: "46. What do you call the Sovereign’s representative in the provinces?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Lieutenant-Governor. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 47, question: "47. What do you mark on a federal election ballot?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: 'An "X". (correct answer)', image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 48, question: "48. What does Confederation mean?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Joining of provinces to make a new country. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 49,
    question: "49. What does it mean to say Canada is a constitutional monarchy?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Canada's Head of State is a hereditary Sovereign (Queen or King) who reigns in accordance with the Constitution. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 50,
    question: "50. What does the “right to a secret ballot” mean?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "No one can watch your vote and no one should look at how you voted (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 51,
    question: "51. What does the Canadian flag look like?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "White with a red border on each end and a red maple leaf in the centre. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 52,
    question: "52. What does the term “responsible government” mean?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "The ministers of the Crown must have the support of a majority of the elected representatives in order to govern. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 53, question: "53. What does the word “Inuit” mean?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: '"The people" in the Inuktitut language. (correct answer)', image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 54,
    question: "54. What happened at the Battle of the Plains of Abraham?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "The British defeated the French marking the end of France's empire in America (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 55, question: "55. What is a Francophone?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "A person who speaks French as their first language (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 56, question: "56. What is a major river in Quebec?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "St. Lawrence River (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 57,
    question: "57. What is a majority government?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "When the party in power holds at least half of the seats in the House of Commons. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 58, question: "58. What is a voter information card?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "A form that tells you when and where to vote. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 59, question: "59. What is Canada’s national winter sport?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Hockey. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 60, question: "60. What is Canada’s system of government called?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Parliamentary government. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 61, question: "61. What is meant by the equality of women and men?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Men and women are equal under the law. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 62, question: "62. What is the “head tax”?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Race-based entry fee charged for Chinese entering Canada. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 63, question: "63. What is the capital city of Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Ottawa. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 64,
    question: "64. What is the difference between the role of the Sovereign and that of the Prime Minister?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer:
      "The Sovereign is the guardian of Constitutional freedoms, the Prime Minister selects the Cabinet ministers and is responsible for operations and policy of government. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 65, question: "65. What is the government of all of Canada called?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Federal. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 66, question: "66. What is the highest court in Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "The Supreme Court of Canada (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 67, question: "67. What is the highest military honour a Canadian can receive?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Victoria Cross. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 68, question: "68. What is the largest religious affiliation in Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Catholic. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 69,
    question: "69. What is the meaning of the Remembrance Day poppy?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "To remember the sacrifice of Canadians who have served or died in wars up to the present day. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 70, question: "70. What is the name of the Governor General?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Richard Wagner. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 71,
    question: "71. What is the name of the Prime Minister of Canada and his/her party?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Justin Trudeau (Liberal Party). (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 72, question: "72. What is the name of the Royal Anthem of Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "God Save the Queen (or King). (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 73, question: "73. What is the role of the courts in Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "To settle disputes. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 74,
    question: "74. What is the role of the Opposition parties?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "To oppose or try to improve government proposals. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 75,
    question: "75. What is the significance of the discovery of insulin by Sir Frederick Banting and Charles Best?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Insulin has saved 16 million lives worldwide. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 76,
    question: "76. What part of the Constitution legally protects the basic rights and freedoms of all Canadians?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "The Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 77, question: "77. What percentage of Aboriginal people are First Nations?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "65%. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 78,
    question: "78. What should you do if you do not receive a voter information card telling you when and where to vote?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Call Elections Canada or visit their website. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 79, question: "79. What song is Canada’s national anthem?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "O Canada. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 80, question: "80. What three oceans border Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Atlantic, Arctic and Pacific. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 81,
    question: "81. What was the “Underground Railroad”?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "An anti-slavery network that helped thousands of slaves escape the United States and settle in Canada (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 82,
    question: "82. What was the significance of June 6, 1944 invasion of Normandy?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Canadians made a significant contribution to the defeat of Nazism and Fascism in Europe during the Second World War. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 83, question: "83. What was the Women’s Suffrage Movement?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "The effort by women to achieve the right to vote. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 84,
    question: "84. What will you promise when you take the Oath of Citizenship?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Pledge allegiance to the Queen, observe the laws of Canada and fulfil the duties of a Canadian. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 85, question: "85. What year did Newfoundland and Labrador join Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "1949 (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 86, question: "86. What year was Confederation?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "1867. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 87, question: "87. When asked, who must you tell how you voted in a federal election?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "No one. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 88, question: "88. When did the British North America Act come into effect?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "1867. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 89,
    question: "89. When did the Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms become part of the Canadian Constitution?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "1982. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 90,
    question: "90. When is Canada Day and what does it celebrate?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "We celebrate the anniversary of Confederation July 1st of each year. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 91, question: "91. When is Remembrance Day celebrated?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "November 11th. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 92,
    question: "92. When must federal elections be held?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "On the third Monday in October every four years following the most recent general election. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 93,
    question: "93. When you vote on election day, what do you do?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer:
      "Go to the voting station with your voter's card and ID, mark an X next to your chosen candidate, fold the ballot and present it to the poll officials who will tear off the ballot number and give you the ballot to deposit in the box (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 94, question: "94. Where are the Great Lakes?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Between Ontario and the United States (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 95, question: "95. Where are the Parliament Buildings located?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Ottawa. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 96, question: "96. Where do most French-speaking Canadians live?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Quebec. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 97, question: "97. Where does Canada rank in the world’s largest countries?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Second (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 98,
    question: "98. Which Act granted, for the first time in Canada, legislative assemblies elected by the people?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "The Constitutional Act of 1791. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 99, question: "99. Which animal is an official symbol of Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "The beaver. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 100, question: "100. Which country borders Canada on the south?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "United States of America. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 101, question: "101. Which federal political party is in power?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Liberal Party. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 102, question: "102. Which of the following is NOT a feature of Canada’s system of government?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Dictatorship. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 103,
    question: "103. Which of the following sentences best describes the War of 1812?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "The USA invaded Canada and was defeated, which ensured that Canada would remain independent of the United States. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 104,
    question: "104. Which of the following statements about residential schools is NOT true?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "The schools were welcomed by the Aboriginal people. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 105, question: "105. Which party becomes the Official Opposition?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "The party with the second most MPs. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 106, question: "106. Which party is the Official Opposition at the federal level?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "The Conservative Party. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 107, question: "107. Which port is the largest and busiest in Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "The Port of Vancouver (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 108, question: "108. Which province has its own time zone?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Newfoundland and Labrador (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 109, question: "109. Which province in Canada is the smallest in land size?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Prince Edward Island. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 110, question: "110. Which province is the main producer of pulp and paper and hydro-electricity?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Quebec (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 111, question: "111. Which province is the only officially bilingual province?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "New Brunswick. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 112, question: "112. Which province was split into two at Confederation?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "The Province of Canada (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 113, question: "113. Which province was the first to grant voting rights to women?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Manitoba (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 114, question: "114. Which provincial flag features the fleur-de-lys?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Quebec (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 115, question: "115. Which region covers more than one-third of Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Northern Territories. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 116,
    question: "116. Which region is known as the industrial and manufacturing heartland of Canada?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Central Canada. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 117,
    question: "117. Which region of Canada is known for both its fertile agricultural land and valuable energy resources?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Prairie provinces. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 118, question: "118. Which three countries are signatories to NAFTA?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Canada, Mexico and the United States. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 119, question: "119. Which was the last province to join Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Newfoundland. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 120, question: "120. Who are the Aboriginal peoples of Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "The first people to live in Canada (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 121,
    question: "121. Who are the Acadians?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "The descendants of French colonists who began settling in what are now the Maritime provinces in 1604. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 122, question: "122. Who are the founding peoples of Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Aboriginal, French and British. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 123, question: "123. Who are the Métis?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "A distinct people of mixed Aboriginal and European ancestry. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 124, question: "124. Who are the Quebecers?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "People of Quebec. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 125,
    question: "125. Who do Canadians vote for in a federal election?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "A candidate they want to represent them in Parliament. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 126,
    question: "126. Who do Members of Parliament represent?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Everyone who lives in his or her electoral district. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 127,
    question: "127. Who had played an important part in building the Canadian Pacific Railway (CPR)?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Chinese railroad workers. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 128,
    question: "128. Who has the right to run as a candidate in federal elections?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Any Canadian citizen who is at least 18 years old. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 129,
    question: "129. Who has the right to vote in federal elections?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "A Canadian citizen, 18 years or older, and on voters' list. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 130, question: "130. Who have major responsibilities on First Nations reserves?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Band chiefs and councillors. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 131, question: "131. Who is Canada’s Head of State?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Her Majesty Queen Elizabeth II. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 132, question: "132. Who is considered the father of Manitoba?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Louis Riel (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 133, question: "133. Who is General Sir Arthur Currie?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Canada's greatest soldier in the First World War. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 134, question: "134. Who is the Head of Government?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "The Prime Minister (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 135, question: "135. Who is the leader of the Federal Official Opposition Party?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Erin O'Toole (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 136, question: "136. Who is the Queen’s representative in Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Governor General of Canada. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 137, question: "137. Who led an armed uprising and seized Fort Garry?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Louis Riel (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 138, question: "138. Who led Quebec into Confederation?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Sir George-Étienne Cartier (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 139,
    question: "139. Who was Sir Louis-Hippolyte La Fontaine?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "A champion of democracy and French language rights and the first leader of a responsible government in the Canadas. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 140, question: "140. Who was Sir Sam Steele?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "A great frontier hero, Mounted Policeman and soldier of the Queen. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 141,
    question: "141. Who was the first leader of a responsible government in the Canadas in 1849?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Sir Louis-Hippolyte La Fontaine. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 142, question: "142. Who was the first Prime Minister of Canada?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Sir John A. Macdonald. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 143,
    question: "143. Who were the United Empire Loyalists?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Settlers who came to Canada from the United States during the American Revolution. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 144, question: "144. Who were the Voyagers?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Montreal-based traders who travelled by canoe (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 145,
    question: "145. Why is the battle of Vimy Ridge important?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Canadian Corps secured its reputation for valour and bravery. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 146,
    question: "146. Why is trade with other countries important to Canada?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "It enhances our economy and raises our standard of living. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 147, question: "147. What is the name of the Lieutenant-Governor of Quebec?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Honourable J. Michel Doyon (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 148, question: "148. What is the capital city of Alberta?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Edmonton. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 149, question: "149. What is the name of the leader of the Opposition in Alberta?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Rachel Notley. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 150, question: "150. What is the name of the Lieutenant-Governor of Alberta?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Salma Lakhani. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 151, question: "151. What is the name of the Premier of Alberta?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Premier Jason Kenney. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 152, question: "152. Which political party is in power in Alberta?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "United Conservative Party (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 153,
    question: "153. Which three natural resources are important to Alberta’s economy today?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Oil, agriculture, and forestry. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 154,
    question: "154. Name the federal electoral districts in Richmond, British Columbia.",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Richmond has two federal electoral districts: Richmond Centre and Steveston-Richmond East (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 155,
    question: "155. Name the members of Parliament for Richmond, British Columbia and the parties they belong to (Richmond Centre, Steveston-Richmond East respectively).",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Alice Wong (Conservative), Kenny Chiu (Conservative) (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 156,
    question:
      "156. Name the Members of the Legislative Assembly for Richmond, British Columbia and the parties they belong to (Richmond North Centre, Richmond South Centre, Richmond-Steveston, and Richmond-Queensborough respectively).",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Teresa Wat (Richmond North Centre), Henry Yao (Richmond South Centre), Kelly Greene(Richmond-Steveston), Aman Singh (Richmond-Queensborough). (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 157,
    question: "157. Name three city councillors for Richmond, British Columbia.",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Harold Steves, Chak Au and Carol Day (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 158, question: "158. What is the capital city of British Columbia?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Victoria. (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 159, question: "159. What is the name of the leader of the Opposition in British Columbia?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Shirley Bond (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 160, question: "160. What is the name of the Lieutenant-Governor of British Columbia?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Janet Austin (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 161, question: "161. What is the name of the Mayor of Richmond, British Columbia?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Mayor Malcolm Brodie (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 162, question: "162. What is the name of the Premier of British Columbia?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Premier John Horgan (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 163, question: "163. Which political party is in power in British Columbia?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "New Democratic Party (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 164,
    question: "164. Which three natural resources are important to British Columbia’s economy today?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Forests, fish and water. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 165,
    question: "165. Why is British Columbia known as Canada’s Pacific Gateway?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Billions of dollars in trade goods are handled through the Port of Vancouver. (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 166, question: "166. What is the capital city of Manitoba?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Winnipeg (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 167, question: "167. What is the name of the leader of the Opposition in Manitoba?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Wab Kinew (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 168, question: "168. What is the name of the Lieutenant-Governor of Manitoba?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Honourable Janice Filmon (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 169, question: "169. What is the name of the Premier of Manitoba?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Premier Brian Pallister (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 170,
    question: "170. What three industries are important to Manitoba’s economy today?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Agriculture, mining and hydro-electric power generation (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 171, question: "171. Which political party is in power in Manitoba?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Progressive Conservative (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 172, question: "172. What is the capital city of New Brunswick?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Fredericton (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 173, question: "173. What is the name of the leader of the Opposition in New Brunswick?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Roger Melanson (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 174, question: "174. What is the name of the Lieutenant-Governor of New Brunswick?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Honourable Brenda Murphy (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 175, question: "175. What is the name of the Premier of New Brunswick?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Premier Blaine Higgs (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 176,
    question: "176. What three industries are important to New Brunswick’s economy today?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Forestry, agriculture and mining (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 177, question: "177. Which political party is in power in New Brunswick?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Progressive Conservative (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 178, question: "178. What is the capital city of Newfoundland and Labrador?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "St. John's (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 179,
    question: "179. What is the name of the leader of the Opposition in Newfoundland and Labrador?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Ches Crosbie (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 180,
    question: "180. What is the name of the Lieutenant-Governor of Newfoundland and Labrador?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Honourable Judy May Foote (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 181, question: "181. What is the name of the Premier of Newfoundland and Labrador?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Premier Andrew Furey (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 182,
    question: "182. What three industries are important to Newfoundland and Labrador’s economy today?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Fisheries, oil and gas extraction (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 183, question: "183. Which political party is in power in Newfoundland and Labrador?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Liberal Party (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 184, question: "184. What is the capital City of Nova Scotia?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Halifax (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 185, question: "185. What is the name of the leader of the Opposition in Nova Scotia?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Tim Houston (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 186, question: "186. What is the name of the Lieutenant-Governor of Nova Scotia?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Honourable Arthur J. LeBlanc (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 187, question: "187. What is the name of the Premier of Nova Scotia?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Premier Iain Rankin (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 188,
    question: "188. What three industries are important to Nova Scotia’s economy today?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Coal mining, forestry and agriculture (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 189, question: "189. Which political party is in power in Nova Scotia?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Liberal (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 190, question: "190. What is the capital City of the Northwest Territories?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Yellowknife (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 191,
    question: "191. What is the name of the Commissioner of the Northwest Territories?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Honourable Margaret Thom (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 192, question: "192. What is the name of the leader of the Opposition in the Northwest Territories?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "None (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 193, question: "193. What is the name of the Premier of the Northwest Territories?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Premier Caroline Cochrane (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 194, question: "194. Which political party is in power in the Northwest Territories?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Governed by consensus (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 195, question: "195. What is the capital City of the Nunavut?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Iqaluit (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 196, question: "196. What is the name of the Commissioner of Nunavut?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Honourable Nellie Taptaqut Kusugak (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 197, question: "197. What is the name of the leader of the Opposition in Nunavut?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "None (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 198, question: "198. What is the name of the Premier of Nunavut?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Premier Joe Savikataaq (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 199, question: "199. Which political party is in power in Nunavut?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Governed by consensus (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 200, question: "200. What is the capital city of Ontario?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Toronto (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 201, question: "201. What is the name of the leader of the Opposition in Ontario?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Andrea Horwath (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 202, question: "202. What is the name of the Lieutenant-Governor of Ontario?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Elizabeth Dowdeswell (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 203, question: "203. What is the name of the Premier of Ontario?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Premier Doug Ford (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 204,
    question: "204. What three industries are important to Ontario’s economy today?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Mining, tourism, automobile manufacturing (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 205, question: "205. Which political party is in power in Ontario?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Progressive Conservative Party (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 206,
    question: "206. Which three are Members of Ontario’s Legislative Assembly?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Rod Phillips, Todd Smith, Michael Coteau (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 207,
    question: "207. Which three are members of Parliament for Ottawa, Ontario?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "David McGuinty, Mona Fortier, Catherine McKenna (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 208, question: "208. What is the capital City of the Prince Edward Island?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Charlottetown (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 209,
    question: "209. What is the name of the leader of the Opposition in Prince Edward Island?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Peter Bevan-Baker (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  {
    id: 210,
    question: "210. What is the name of the Lieutenant-Governor of Prince Edward Island?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Honourable Antoinette Perry (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 211, question: "211. What is the name of the Premier of Prince Edward Island?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Premier Dennis King (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 212, question: "212. Which political party is in power in Prince Edward Island?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Progressive Conservative (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 213, question: "213. What is the capital City of the Quebec?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Quebec City (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 214, question: "214. What is the name of the leader of the Opposition in Quebec?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Dominique Anglade (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 215, question: "215. What is the name of the Premier of Quebec ?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Premier Francois Legault (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 216,
    question: "216. What three industries are important to Quebec’s economy today?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Pulp and paper, forestry and hydro-electric power (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 217, question: "217. Which political party is in power in Quebec?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Coalition Avenir Québec (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 218, question: "218. What is the capital city of Saskatchewan?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Regina (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 219, question: "219. What is the name of the leader of the Opposition in Saskatchewan?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Ryan Meili (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 220, question: "220. What is the name of the Lieutenant-Governor of Saskatchewan?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Honourable Russ Mirasty (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 221, question: "221. What is the name of the Premier of Saskatchewan?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Premier Scott Moe (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  {
    id: 222,
    question: "222. What three industries are important to Saskatchewan’s economy today?",
    answers: [],
    correnctAnswer: "Farming, mining and natural gas (correct answer)",
    image: "",
    explanation: "",
  },
  { id: 223, question: "223. Which political party is in power in Saskatchewan?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Saskatchewan Party (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 224, question: "224. What is the capital city of Yukon Territory?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Whitehorse (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 225, question: "225. What is the name of the Commissioner of Yukon Territory?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Honourable Angélique Bernard (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 226, question: "226. What is the name of the leader of the Opposition in Yukon Territory?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Stacey Hassard (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 227, question: "227. What is the name of the Premier of Yukon Territory?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Premier Sandy Silver (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
  { id: 228, question: "228. Which political party is in power in Yukon Territory?", answers: [], correnctAnswer: "Liberal (correct answer)", image: "", explanation: "" },
];

export default all_questions;
